This is a story
about two kingdoms
side by side,
but worlds apart.
All along the border
magical flowers grew.
Primroses bloom
between light and shadow.
They are used to
make love potion.
Because after all
everybody deserves
to be loved.
Ooh!
Whoa!
Okay...
♪ Wise men say
♪ Only fools
♪ Only fools rush in
Oh!
♪ But I can't help
♪ Falling in love with you
♪ Shall I say
♪ Would it be
Would it be a sin
Sorry.
♪ That I can't help
♪ Falling in love with you ♪
What?
Primroses.
Oh, no. I didn't mean to.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
Was she trying to
get a primrose petal?
We better tell him.
He's not gonna be very happy.
Let me handle it.
I'll tell him.
Good idea!
Sire! News from the border!
You tell him.
Huh? Okay.
A fairy flew
into our forest.
What?
And almost took a primrose.
A primrose?
I hate this time of year.
Spring.
Send more goblins
to cut down every primrose.
No primroses,
no potion.
No potion,
no love.
Because love
is dangerous.
It weakens, it rots.
It destroys order.
And without order,
what is left?
Chaos.
Destroy the primroses!
Or I will destroy you.
Whoa.
Stuff.
Griselda. Ooh!
I need your help.
No.
You know how
your boss, my son,
is making everyone miserable
with his ban on love?
No.
Don't you want to see love
return to the Dark Forest?
No.
But I found him
the perfect...
I told you to stay
out of the light!
Roland! Oh, thank goodness!
Whoa!
Aren't you supposed
to be getting ready
for our wedding?
I will. I am!
Oh, wait!
I have something for you!
For me? Why, aren't you
just the sweetest...
Whoa!
Marianne? You're in a plant.
You can't look at me!
I forgot.
Bad luck on our wedding day.
Well, too bad you can't
see me.
My hair is doing
that thing we both love.
Ahh! Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Were you in the Dark Forest?
No! Maybe. Yes.
You could've been killed.
No! Don't look.
Or worse,
seriously disfigured.
Hey! I can take
care of myself.
That is no place
for a princess.
Oh, yeah? How about
a princess that can do this?
Marianne,
don't play with...
Wow!
Who's the big girl?
You got a sword. Yep.
Okay.
Yeah, but I don't
need a sword.
Because when
I rule this kingdom,
I'll go into that Dark Forest
to talk to them.
To make it so, at long last,
we're not scared anymore.
That is so sweet.
And then we can all go
anywhere we want
to have fun, to see things,
to have adventures!
I'll be your adventure.
Come on, Marianne,
my future queen.
Aw...
My future king.
Yeah...
King. I'll have an army.
Ooh!
Yeah. Wait, what?
Parry. Lunge.
Um...
To protect
the Fairy Kingdom,
and you,
my little buttercup.
Mmm.
Now, go get yourself
all prettified.
Today has got to be perfect.
Chipper! Let's ride.
Marianne!
What?
Remember the wedding?
I know.
We have to get ready!
What's with your hair?
I know.
We don't have much time!
I know!
Ugh! What's that?
A boutonniere.
Oh! I forgot to
give this to Roland.
You can't
give him that.
Why not?
Uh, he's too good-looking?
Yeah.
I'll fix that.
Thanks, sis.
Ew!
Dawn!
Do you think
that Roland loves me
as much as I love him?
Oh, Marianne.
How could he not love you?
You're so
totally loveable!
Really?
I wish you could
see how you look.
♪ Oh, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ He's got you
looking crazy in love
♪ Yeah, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ Looking so crazy, got you
looking so crazy in love ♪
It's perfect.
You're welcome.
I wanna give this
to him now!
Isn't it bad luck
if he sees you...
♪ Oh, I
♪ Can't help
♪ Falling in love with you
Uh-oh.
♪ Uh-oh, uh-oh
♪ As the river flows
♪ Surely to the sea
♪ Darling, so it goes
♪ Some things
♪ Are meant to be
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Some things are
meant to be
♪ Take my hand
♪ Oh, take my hand
♪ Take my whole life, too
♪ For I can't help
♪ Falling in love with you
♪ Oh, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ He's got you
looking crazy in love
♪ Oh, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ Looking so crazy, got me
looking so crazy in love
♪ Oh, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ He's got you
looking crazy in love
Hey! Marianne!
♪ Oh, you're looking
crazy in love
♪ And I can't help it
♪ No, I can't help it
♪ I can't help it
♪ And no, I
♪ I
♪ Can't help
♪ No, I can't help
♪ Falling in love
♪ With you
♪ So crazy,
crazy in love, yeah
♪ And no I know I can't help
♪ No, I
♪ Falling in love ♪
Roland!
I am so
not getting my army.
Marianne?
Dawn.
What happened?
I...
I don't wanna talk about it.
Not even to me?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
But wait.
Wait!
Tell Dad
the wedding's off.
The wedding's off?
♪ What do you get
when you fall in love?
♪ A guy with a pin
to burst your bubble
♪ That's what you get
♪ For all your trouble
♪ I'll never fall in love
♪ Again
♪ What do you get
when you kiss a boy?
♪ You get enough germs
to catch a fever
♪ Then straight away
he'll up and leave you
♪ I'll
♪ Never fall in love again
♪ No,
I'll never fall in love again
♪ Don't tell me
what it's all about
♪ All about
♪ 'Cause I've been there
And I'm glad I'm out
♪ Out of those chains
Those chains that bind you
♪ That is why
I'm here to remind you
♪ Here to remind you
♪ What do you get
when you give your heart?
♪ You get it all
broken up and battered
♪ Yeah, that's what you get
♪ A heart that's shattered
♪ I'll never
fall in love again
♪ No, I'll
♪ Never fall in love again
♪ Never fall in love again ♪
Dawn!
Dawn! Where are you?
The coast is clear.
Shh! She'll hear you.
Whatever happened
that wedding day
must have been really bad.
Yeah, bad.
Because now she's always
hovering, watching, worrying.
What's she trying
to protect me from?
You can take care
of yourself.
Yeah. So...
Spring Ball.
Yeah.
My first dance.
Yeah!
What's your plan?
I made it so when
the music starts,
you'll "accidentally"
bump into Hadrian.
Ooh!
Oh! Today is
gonna be so exciting!
Mmm. It already is.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What?
Hadrian?
Yeah, Hadrian.
The guy with the great,
red, wavy hair.
No, no, no.
I don't have a crush on him.
I really like Nathan.
Okay. I gotta find Hadrian,
tell Hadrian to
stand in a new place,
find Nathan and tell him
to stand in the old place
Hadrian was standing in.
What if he doesn't like me?
What?
Snap out of it! Listen.
Like I always say...
♪ Don't worry
Maybe he thinks
I'm too perky.
♪ About a thing
Or dance funny?
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
Or my hair is too poufy?
♪ Don't you worry
About a thing
♪ About a thing
♪ Oh, 'cause
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
All right!
♪ Woke up this morning
♪ Smiled at the rising sun
♪ Three little birds
♪ Pitch by my doorstep
♪ Singin' sweet songs
♪ Of melodies pure and true
♪ Sayin'
♪ This is my message to you
♪ Oh, don't worry
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
Sunny.
Dawn, I'm trying to sing.
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
Sunny.
Yes!
♪ Don't worry about a thing ♪
Sunny?
What?
Worry!
No, no, no!
Hey! Watch the ears!
Help!
Help! We've gotta get help!
You're looking at it.
Ahh! Sunny!
Too short to run!
Too young to die!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Marianne!
Are you crazy?
Sunny, go right!
Sunny, duck!
Okay!
Dawn, some help here.
What am I gonna
do with you?
Sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
Pull your head
out of the clouds!
Clouds full of boys.
I can't help it.
You just have no idea
what's going on around you.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Where's Sunny?
You were
in the Dark Forest!
I was?
He was?
Do you want
what happened
to the Sugar Plum Fairy
to happen to you?
No!
No, no!
Locked away forever
because she made
love potion from...
Primroses!
We have to get
out of here now!
That place...
Marianne?
Hello?
Marianne!
We're gonna be late
for the Spring Ball!
You drive me crazy!
We have to get
out of here, now.
I just said that.
So, that's how you react
to a near-death
experience?
Ugh!
What?
You were both
nearly killed.
You make such a big deal
out of everything.
Whoa! I'm a total mess!
We have to get
ready for the ball.
Ha! No, you've gotta
get ready for the ball.
Uh, you're going like that?
Good luck being
asked to dance.
I'm not dancing.
I'm gonna dance
with the most perfect boy.
And who would that be?
Aaron?
No.
Benjamin. Charles.
Darren!
No.
Gordon? Herbert?
I'm going alphabetical,
if that helps.
Hi.
Smile, my dear. Smile.
A real smile.
This is one of my better ones.
You used to love
the Spring Ball.
Dad, I'm just
too old for this.
I just want to see the happy
Marianne I used to know.
Before the...
The Roland misunderstanding.
I'm happy.
Well, I hope you're
happy enough to dance
with your father.
Or someone
even better.
♪ Here I am
Roland!
♪ On my knees again
Dad!
♪ I'd do anything
He's so romantic.
♪ Just to make it right
I'm so onto
that hair thing.
♪ Say you'll understand
Never!
♪ I know you can
Oh, no, I can't!
♪ Come on, Marianne
You cheated on me, remember?
You left me at the altar,
remember?
♪ No matter what people say
♪ It didn't happen that way
♪ She was a passing fling
♪ And not a permanent thing
Oh, really?
♪ So I hang my head
Oh, I wish that I was dead
I can help with that.
♪ Come on, Marianne
Hi. I'm Dawn.
Come on, Marianne.
♪ Come on...
♪ Marianne
♪ Say you can understand
♪ My Marianne ♪
Ugh! I'm not your anything.
Hey. One little mistake.
Little?
You got a lot of
nerve walking in here.
♪ Think you got
the best of me
♪ Think you had
the last laugh
No.
♪ Bet you think
that everything
♪ Good is gone
Hold on there, darling.
♪ Think you
left me broken down
♪ Think that I'd come
running back
Well...
♪ Baby, you don't know me
'cause you're dead wrong
Okay, slow down there,
Marianne.
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger
♪ Stand a little taller
♪ Doesn't mean I'm lonely
♪ When I'm alone
♪ What does not kill you
makes a fighter
Whoa! Watch the face!
♪ Footsteps even lighter
Whoa, whoa.
Come on, I mean, seriously.
♪ Doesn't mean I'm over
'cause you're gone ♪
Whoa!
♪ Here I am
Oh, there you go.
♪ On my knees again
On your knees again.
♪ I'll do anything
just to make it right
Yeah, right.
♪ Say you'll understand
Only too well.
♪ Oh, I know you can
♪ Come on, Marianne
♪ Didn't think
that I'd come back
♪ I'd come back swinging
Buttercup.
Oops.
Cheater,
cheater, cheater!
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger
Back up! Back up! Hey!
♪ Stand a little taller
♪ Doesn't mean I'm lonely
when I'm alone
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes a fighter
♪ Footsteps even lighter
♪ Doesn't mean I'm over
'cause you're gone
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, stronger
Don't bruise the jewels!
♪ Just me, myself and I
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger
♪ Stand a little taller
What are you
trying to say?
♪ Well, now it's time to say
♪ Goodbye ♪
Bye-bye.
Now, that was fun!
Awkward.
Ugh!
Whoa!
Marianne slammed
him pretty good.
Well, so much
for being king.
Ouch!
You think I can't be king?
King Roland!
Well...
Uh, wouldn't he have to
marry Marianne?
Yes, and he will.
All we have to do is
get some of that love potion.
You saying I need
a love potion?
No, no, just kidding!
It was just a joke.
We gotta go.
Just kidding, boss!
Okay.
All I gotta do is visualize.
Visualize.
The crown,
sitting right on top...
♪ I wanna dance
with somebody
♪ I wanna feel
the beat with somebody
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance
Hi!
♪ With somebody
who loves me ♪
You okay?
Who, me? Okay?
Yes, I am.
No.
Hey, elf.
I know just how you feel.
Yeah. Marianne
slammed you pretty good.
Aw! You got it bad.
I wish there was a way to
make her fall in love with me.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Like, I don't know, maybe
something like a love potion.
Like a love potion!
Great idea!
It is a great idea.
Except only
the Sugar Plum Fairy
can make the potion.
She's locked away
in the Dark Forest
and nobody ever goes
into the Dark Forest!
But I know you can.
But why can't you?
Because I'm big!
My armor, it's too shiny.
I'd be spotted for sure.
If only I was little,
like you.
Uh-huh.
And I could blend in.
Like you.
I do blend in.
Oh, it would
have been perfect!
Then we both,
you know, me and you,
both used the love potion.
I'll do it!
You will?
If you stop crying.
What? Oh, I'm much better now.
My plan is perfect!
All I gotta do is
find a primrose flower,
get to the castle
where I'll find
the Sugar Plum Fairy.
She'll make her love potion
with all the little
primrose petals that I...
Man, those goblins work fast!
Uh-oh.
Petal, petal, petal.
Think quick, think!
Ah! Duh.
All right.
A small elf
is in the Dark Forest.
A small elf is in
the Dark Forest.
Oh! Got it!
Thang! Thang!
What does it mean?
I'm listening.
News from the mushrooms, sire.
You can tell him.
You tell him.
He likes you.
Really?
Now I'm waiting!
A tall chef is
into shark storage!
What?
Okay, you know how
we sometimes have a shark,
but no place to store it?
Well, a very tall chef
has that very same problem.
Hmm. That doesn't
make any sense.
I'll deal with it!
Ahem.
What?
That was close.
A small elf is in
the Dark Forest!
Well, if he's looking
for trouble,
he's come to the right place.
♪ Yeah
♪ If he's looking for trouble
♪ Just take
a look at this face
♪ Because I'm evil
Yeah.
♪ My middle name is misery
♪ Yes, I'm evil
♪ So don't you
mess around with me ♪
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
♪ 'Cause every little
thing is gonna be... ♪
♪ Woke up this morning
♪ I hope I woke up
this morning
♪ Three goblins
♪ Sayin' I'm
going to kill you ♪
Oh! Okay, you got me!
Just kill me now.
Make it quick.
Hey! Hey, wait a minute.
Did you tie my...
Who are you?
Hmm.
Okay, look,
you little thing,
I'm a guy who usually
enjoys a good joke,
even at my own expense.
But right now, I'm not in
a "ha-ha" frame of mind.
I'm in an "Ah!"
frame of mind.
Ah!
I am on a very
serious mission!
I really gotta find
the Sugar Plum Fairy,
the maker of
the all-powerful love potion,
and you're holding
me back. Ow!
You know where she is?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What?
Oh. Okay.
Wait a minute.
You ain't gonna
trick me again, are you?
Good. Because I'm an elf,
and we're very
trusting creatures.
So here's me,
trusting you.
Marianne!
Kinda busy.
I deserved that one.
The Elves' Spring Dance
is starting soon.
I want you...
After the last dance?
You kidding me?
Oh, Marianne.
You're...
You're a unique girl.
And Roland
may have a few flaws...
Understatement.
But he still loves you.
He loves the crown.
But...
And his hair.
But, but...
Not in that order.
But if not Roland,
then there has to
be someone else!
No, there doesn't.
Maybe if you got
out more often.
Let it go, Dad.
You'll be a stronger ruler
with a king at your side.
I'm stronger alone.
I don't want you to be alone.
Dad, I promise
if I find a guy out there
who takes my hand
and looks me in the eye
and I don't
want to hit him...
I'll consider it.
But that guy doesn't exist.
Then go to the dance to
help me keep an eye on that
flirtatious sister of yours.
That's my girl!
Did you find him?
I thought
I heard something.
If you see him, kill him.
I won't fit.
Come on.
She's that scary?
Whoa!
Hello?
Are you the Sugar Plum Fairy?
I expected something more
purple.
Hello?
A primrose?
It is!
I brought it so you can...
Nuh-uh.
So you can make...
The love potion.
How do you think
I got in here?
Shh! Listen, my name is Sunny.
The Bog King
won't listen to me
about what happened
on that fateful day.
And I've been
locked away for so long.
"That fateful day"?
You were listening!
So I'll do it.
Yes!
If
you promise to set me free!
What?
Shake on it?
Uh...
You can reach in.
I can't reach out.
You should see your face!
Oh, wait. I can show you!
Another good one!
Wanna see?
No, no, no.
Petal.
Plumettes!
Believe you me,
there can be
unforeseen consequences.
Like what?
♪ Love
♪ Love is strange
Uh, now's not
the time for a concert.
♪ Many people
Shh! Whoa!
♪ Take it for a game
No lookie-loos!
♪ Once you get it
Ah!
♪ You're in an awful...
What did I say?
No looking... No... Mmm-mmm.
♪ 'Cause after you've had it
♪ You never wanna quit
If you think making
the potion's dangerous,
wait till you use it.
♪ Love is strange
♪ Love
♪ Is strange
Oh! I'm so good,
it scares me so!
Is the elf taken care of?
He's a slippery
little devil.
He's just an elf!
Hi!
Mom, no.
Oh, relax your thorax.
Feast your eyes on...
No.
Maxine's into fungi.
No!
Lakeesha's hobby
is killing frogs.
Mom!
All you need
is somebody to...
Don't say it.
What is it with men?
They can't say
that word, lo...
This is what
I get for carrying you
23 months in my womb?
Promise to stop talking?
Mmm-hmm.
♪ Love!
♪ Once you get it
♪ You're in an awful fix
Whoops! I almost
forgot the last step!
♪ But after you've had it
♪ You never wanna quit
Directions.
Dust the one you love.
Stand in front.
Be the first she sees
when she opens her eyes.
Got it.
Dust the first eyes you see,
be in the front,
and stand on the one you love!
Now, pull!
Sunny?
Yeah?
I know what
set me free.
Me.
♪ Love is strange
Oh!
♪ Love
♪ Is strange ♪
Stop!
Sugar Plum? She can't be.
Now.
Slowly.
I'm free!
Quiet! We're gonna
get caught!
I'm free!
Free?
We're still in the dungeon!
Free!
Whoa!
Totally nuts.
I'm free.
Did I mention I'm free?
Quietly.
Wait!
What? Where?
How did you find me?
An imp.
The imp?
Oh, he wants the potion.
Loves to spread it around
like goblin dung.
Ugh!
Hey!
What?
Never let this imp
get that potion!
Okay.
No, no, no.
Thang, sound the alarm.
I'm sorry.
Stuff! Sound the alarm!
Whoa!
I'm free!
No, no!
She's free?
I'm free!
Excuse me, coming through.
Sorry.
All-righty. Excuse me.
Sunny! Hurry!
Oopsie.
Ooh!
Stop that! Shoo! Shoo!
Gotcha!
Yeah!
Huh?
Where did he go?
He disappeared.
Can elves disappear?
If they're magic.
Is he magic?
Well, he disappeared!
Sorry.
This will never happen...
No, no, no!
No!
...again.
Sunny!
Oh!
Remember what I told you!
Hey! Get off!
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry,
but I have to do this!
The Plum warned me
about you!
Oh, no.
Are you okay, little guy?
Little guy?
Oh, good. Bye!
What did you do?
Well, the elf asked me
to make the love potion.
But you didn't
have a primrose petal.
And he brought me
a primrose petal.
You made the potion?
Just like I did for you
on that fateful day you never
ever, ever let me talk about.
Where is he?
Halfway to
the Elf Festival by now.
Who wants to go
to a party tonight?
Yeah!
Booties, prepare to be shaken!
Ha-ha!
Okay, she's here.
Tonight, I surely know,
she will love me.
♪ I say, "Hey!"
♪ I be gone today
♪ But I'll be
back around the way
♪ It seems like
everywhere I go
♪ The more I see,
the less I know
♪ But I know one thing
♪ I love you
♪ I love you, I love you
♪ Been a lot of places
all around the way
♪ I've seen a lot of joy
and I've seen a lot of pain
♪ But I don't want to write
a love song for the world
♪ I just want to write
a song about
a boy and a girl
♪ Hear them on the corner
Always calling my name
What?
Hi, sweet thing.
I'm Roland.
♪ The kids on the corner
playing silly games
What's your name?
♪ When I saw you
getting down, girl,
I hoped it was you
♪ And when I looked into
your eyes I knew it was true
♪ I say, "Hey!"
I be gone today
♪ But I'll be
back around the way
Ugh!
♪ Seems like everywhere I go
Dawn, Roland's here,
so I'm leaving!
Marianne!
Ooh! I'm dancing!
Hey, Roland!
I wish I had boys.
Sunny! Psst!
Sunny! Look here!
♪ I say, "Hey!"
I be gone today
Sunny! Not now.
♪ But I'll be
back around the way
♪ It seems like
everywhere I go
♪ The more I see,
the less I know
♪ But I know one thing
♪ I love you
I love you
I hate this thing!
♪ I say, "Hey!"
I be gone today
♪ But I'll be
back around the way
♪ It seems like
everywhere I go
♪ The more I see,
the less I know
♪ But I know one thing
That I love you
♪ I know!
♪ I love you, I love you
♪ I love you ♪
Ha-ha!
Sunny! No!
This one's too feisty.
Go get the smaller one!
Dawn!
Sunny! Look!
Hi, Sunny!
Dawn!
Hey!
No! Hey!
No!
Love potion? No!
Oh, no! No!
Guards!
Get him!
Got him!
My little girl!
Daddy!
Daddy! Help!
Dawn!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry,
Sugar Plum Fairy.
Where's my potion?
♪ I've been mistreated
♪ I've been abused
♪ I've been trespassed
♪ And invaded
♪ And I am not amused
Dawn! No!
♪ I've been insulted
♪ Disrespected
♪ I've been mistreated
Release my sister,
you scaly-backed cockroach!
Whoa.
Huh?
Return the love potion
by moondown, tough girl.
Or you'll never see
your sister again.
I'll have your
head on a stick!
Take me instead!
I took the love potion!
Sunny!
Then give it back.
I don't have it.
You heard my terms.
By moondown,
or all of you will be next!
♪ I've been insulted
♪ Disrespected
♪ I've been mistreated
♪ I've been insulted
♪ Disrespected
♪ I've been mistreated ♪
A-ha!
Dad?
I forbid you to fly
into the Dark Forest!
Dad, I let this happen!
I have to get her back.
I have to keep you safe.
No need to worry.
I will save the princess!
I was just fighting
a dozen goblins.
Roland! Yes!
Oh, no!
What do you need?
I need an army.
Oh! We can't trust him!
And weapons!
And a trebuchet!
Sunny!
What?
What were...
And a mace.
And a crossbow.
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
What do we do? We have to...
Dawn. She's not strong enough.
She's not going to...
I'll rescue her.
No! No, it's too dangerous.
No, but I can.
No.
I'm the only one who can.
So what do I do?
You get the potion back.
I'll get my sister!
Marianne!
Looks like I gotta
rescue two princesses.
Sunny!
What?
If anything happens
to my daughters,
I'm holding you
personally responsible!
Uh...
This is all your fault!
You nearly got
everyone killed!
Yeah!
I know. I know.
But look.
Dawn, now,
she's my best friend.
But she's our princess!
Now, together we must...
No, no, no.
Together we will rescue Dawn
from the cruel grasp
of the Dark Forest.
Who's with me?
No volunteers?
Pare!
Thanks, man!
Um...
Uh-oh.
Bring me
the prisoner.
I get to rip
her wings off!
I want
the wishbone.
No eating!
Brutus.
Oh!
So, what do we have here?
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
What?
♪ You know that I love you
♪ I can't help myself
Huh?
♪ I love you
and nobody else ♪
♪ But I'm evil
♪ My middle name is misery
♪ Yes, I'm evil
♪ So don't you
mess around with me ♪
Oh, silly.
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
Stop that!
♪ You know that I love you
And stop that!
♪ I can't help myself
I'm a sucker
for sweet, pretty singing.
Shut it off! Shut it off!
♪ When I call your name
♪ Boy, it starts a flame
♪ Burning in my heart
Tearing it apart
The potion.
The potion!
We should have
taken the feisty one!
Get the Sugar Plum!
What's he talking about?
I can't hear
over that singing!
Uh-uh.
♪ Ooh, I can't help myself
♪ I love you
and nobody else
♪ No, I can't help myself ♪
Take her!
And lock this
crazy creature
in the dungeon!
She is crazy
in love with you!
Do I hear wedding bells?
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
I hate princesses.
♪ You know that
I love you ♪
Careful! She's our bait.
Oh, well...
If I have to look
under every rock,
I won't let you
die sad and alone.
Bring me Sugar Plum!
♪ There's no way
♪ I'm gonna sit this one out
♪ I gotta take a chance now
♪ Not be a prisoner of doubt
♪ I'm comin' ♪
Whoa!
Ugh!
Whoo!
Well, you wanted adventure,
and now you got it.
You ready?
Oh, yeah.
Take the other side!
Wait for my signal!
Now!
Ahh! Mmm-mmm.
Huh?
No, he didn't. Huh?
Oh, that's nasty.
Oh, man. At least
it can't get any worse.
It just did.
Oh! So, your eye seems
to be healing pretty good.
Uh! Okay. Stop that!
Aw!
Crazy little thing.
He's kind of cute.
Hey!
I think she likes us!
Come back here!
♪ No, I can't
forget this evening
♪ Or your face
as you were leaving
Oh, don't let
her sunny sweetness
flamflumble you.
Not your type.
Now, I've found someone
who is positively
perfect for you.
Not now, Mother.
♪ Yes, it shows ♪
Eh! I'm not giving up!
Finally.
Griselda.
Plum.
It's so amusing
how you keep trying.
Hmm, you're one to talk,
with your magic
recipe for failure!
Well, the recipe's
working now! Isn't it?
Oh, it works.
I need the antidote!
Oh, it works? Pah!
Then explain what
happened to this one.
Oh, you have
your father's smile!
Wait. I know this song!
Cover up!
♪ I can't live
if living is without you
Give me the antidote!
And what will you do
if I refuse? Lock me away?
♪ I can't live ♪
I can't live!
Everybody, be quiet!
Kill me!
I'll do it myself!
Ooh!
If you don't keep
your mouth shut,
I'm going to rip
your wings off,
my pretty little
fairy princess!
Ha-ha! Flirt!
What is that?
I made it special for you.
For me?
It looks good on you.
Uh, I don't...
I hope you like it.
This isn't...
Well, um, thank you.
It's, uh...
It's lovely.
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
No, no, no!
♪ You know that I love you
What you're feeling
is the potion, you know!
♪ I can't help myself
No, I suppose you don't.
♪ I love you
and nobody else ♪
Please, stop!
You must be tired
from all that singing.
I could sing forever.
Why don't you
take a wee nap?
I promise I won't go far.
Wait!
Please tell me your name.
I am the Bog King!
My Boggy-woggy
Kingy-wingy!
"Bog King!"
Boggy Kingy-wingy.
"King!"
Kingy-wingy.
Good night,
sweet Boggy-woggy.
Good night.
News, your majesty!
Quiet!
She's asleep.
Sorry. There's reports
of lots of creatures being
love-dusted!
Bring them...
Bring them in.
Bring them all in here.
Ah!
Oh!
There you are!
You go that way.
I'm going this way!
Yeah.
Whoo!
Ha-ha!
Hey, you!
Hmm?
No, no, no.
Not you, Lizzie.
That little thing inside.
We caught you
fair and square!
Hand it over!
Hmm...
Oh, yeah, sure.
Go ahead and think.
I'll just wait for you at
the other end of the lizard.
Thanks!
Spit.
♪ This thing called love
♪ I just can't handle it
Who's a good girl?
♪ This thing called love
You're a good girl!
Don't you feel special?
♪ I must get around to it
♪ I ain't ready
♪ Crazy little thing
called love ♪
Okay!
Let's go fetch Dawn.
Who's a good girl?
In such dark as this,
we must be ever vigilant.
Clear!
Clearing is exactly
what we're gonna do
to this foul forest.
We're gonna...
Get ya!
Stealthily,
we shall sneak up on...
Who would live in this?
Wipe that off, will you?
And, lo,
a creature with no face.
It's looking at me.
I don't think
that's possible.
Good point!
Watch for grotesqueries
at every corner.
Imagine the most
unimaginable danger.
That's probably nothing.
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, Roland!
Thank you!
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Wait, wait!
How did you get that to...
She fell in love
with me!
Me, too!
Is that wrong?
I got the love potion.
Wow! Yeah, wow!
You must really
need that potion.
Wait! I got it for...
Dawn! You got it
for Princess Dawn.
Winky-winky.
And well done,
for a little guy.
Squish!
I got it... I got it...
I got it for Dawn.
I better take that
to keep it safe.
Thank you, tiny rabbit!
Whoa!
It's almost moondown.
Hold on, Dawn. I'm coming!
Okay, okay!
Yes! I love her!
You know! Ha-ha-ha!
Come on, Lizzie! Let's go!
Halt!
March!
I lead!
Okay! Okay.
We're gonna get ya!
Help me!
Help!
Mushrooms in love!
Ooh! Kiss me. Quick!
No smooching!
Ugh.
Shush him.
You shush him!
You're closer.
You're right. Shush!
So, why don't you go
and get some sleep?
What were
you thinking?
Don't hate me.
Too late.
And leave me alone.
Nice button-ere.
Not "button-ere."
"Boutonniere."
No,
it's not "boutonniere."
It's "button-ere."
It's "boutonniere."
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Release my sister.
Oh, no!
Not another princess!
Well, at least
you're not singing.
♪ I'm coming
straight on for you
♪ I've made up my mind
Taking a little break?
♪ I'm feeling strong now
♪ Now I'm coming through
Well...
Need any help, sire?
No.
♪ I'm coming
straight on for you
♪ Yeah! Straight on for you
Impressive!
♪ I'm coming
straight on for you ♪
Uh-oh.
♪ Rock-a-bye, fairy
Away in your cell
♪ Scream your head off
But no one can tell ♪
Had enough?
I could
do this all day.
But now, give me
the potion!
The almighty Bog King
needs a magic love potion.
I don't need it!
I want to eradicate it!
Well, eradicate this!
Ask him.
He'll appreciate it.
Okay. Need any help?
No!
Look at you!
Whoa!
Not bad.
Looks like
you need help.
No!
Ha!
Ha-ha!
Ah-ha!
So, is that all you got?
♪ Now I know
♪ How to play my hand
Well, I'm ready for you!
♪ What the winner don't know,
the gambler understands
What does that even mean?
♪ No!
You don't stand a chance
♪ You don't stand a chance
♪ I'm coming
straight on for you
Ooh!
Ah!
You fight well,
for a fairy.
Wish I could say
the same for you!
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I was expecting more.
♪ Straight on for you
♪ Straight on for you ♪
Oh.
Go ahead.
Kill me,
but you won't
get your sister.
Need any help?
No!
♪ Wise men say
♪ Only fools rush in
The beast has awoken.
Oh, no.
What did she
fall in love with?
Would you care to see?
♪ Falling in love with you
Finally.
♪ Like a river flows
See what happens
when love is
loosed upon the world?
♪ Fools rush in
♪ Would it be a sin? ♪
Ew.
Tell them to be quiet.
You tell them.
Your voice cuts through
better than mine.
That's true. Quiet!
Everybody be quiet!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Quiet!
Quiet! Quiet!
Sorry.
I hope you've got
a strong stomach.
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
♪ You know that I love... ♪
You?
Yes.
Antidote?
Working on it.
I know she's a girl
who falls in love with
every guy she sees,
but this is ridiculous!
I, um...
Sire! I forgot
to mention,
you forgot your
weapon upstairs.
But I found
your boutonniere!
Hi.
You know,
I really enjoyed our fight,
but I'll be taking
my sister home now.
Oh, no,
you're not!
Dawn!
Boggy-bear!
"Bog King!"
Let's go back
to our cell. Shall we?
Anything for you,
Boggy-woggy.
Uh, "Bog."
Don't listen to him!
You are not
the boss of me!
And don't even think
about stealing my Boggy!
"Bog!"
She stays here until
I get the potion back.
Forget the potion.
Get the antidote, now!
Well, maybe
you should ask her.
"Her"? Who?
The Sugar Plum Fairy.
Ooh! Welcome!
Give me the antidote.
If you let me talk
about that fateful...
No!
Then, no.
Please! I love my sister.
I need that antidote.
Okay! I'll just need
a few things.
What?
An eye of newt,
a golden lute,
a loom and a flute.
Get those things.
And green beans,
a nail file, a tangelo...
Hey, will it really work?
Eh, who knows?
And you are?
My mother.
Griselda.
Don't
you have a comb?
It's drafty down here.
Come upstairs.
There's snacks.
Well...
♪ I got a feeling
It's the best I could do
on such short notice.
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good night
You two behave.
Toodle-oo!
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good...
Stop.
♪ ...night! Yeah ♪
Go see if
the antidote's ready.
Roger, B.K.
And here's
your boutonniere.
Quickly!
You sang pretty good.
You should see me dance.
I'd love to.
Why would she...
Oh.
Oh!
Who likes this?
Not me!
I hate it!
I hate it more!
Oh, yeah?
They're all fools!
Rushing in.
They can't help it!
They're in chains...
That bind you!
It's nothing but...
Trouble!
It's like their middle name
is misery.
Well...
What's the point?
Bursting bubbles!
That's what they get.
Lies
and more lies!
Pain!
Sorrows!
Wait!
I, uh, actually
like this one.
Oh! Why?
I... I don't know.
Well, it's...
It's
lovely.
I don't wanna
be carrying this.
Antidote's ready, sire.
Well? Where is it?
It's a riddle!
A riddle?
What about all that
stuff you asked for?
Well, you know, in prison,
it's hard to shop!
Would you like to
hear the riddle, or not?
No!
Yes!
Then listen carefully.
The antidote
is the one thing
more powerful
than the potion.
Did she say "antidote"
or "anecdote"?
I hate riddles!
The moon
is sinking fast.
Can we go
maybe a lot faster?
Halt!
What?
Oh, wow!
Did you see that?
I believe that is
the ugliest creature
I have ever seen!
And it was naked!
An army approaches.
Got it! Yes!
What was that again?
Something more powerful...
...than the potion.
That's what I said.
Sire! News from
the mushrooms!
An arm skis on roaches.
Carry on!
How'd you do?
I nailed it!
Something more power...
I'm bored!
I'll just tell you.
Great!
If you set me free.
No!
Okay.
Yeah!
Then I will reveal
the antidote with a story.
What? No!
One fateful day,
when the Bog King
was young and impetuous,
he fell in love with
a sweet young thing.
Ew!
She was the most
beautiful creature
I ever saw.
Seriously?
Hmm.
He was so in love.
But Bog, he had no patience.
That's enough!
So, he came to me
for my love potion.
I tried to tell him
how it worked.
But he dusted the sweet,
unsuspecting creature.
Plum, I beg you.
As she was gazing into
the eyes of a lovesick Bog...
Even with a love potion,
I'm too hideous to love.
You're not hideous.
Hideous,
not hideous, whatever!
But that's not why
the potion didn't work.
What?
She was already in love
with someone else!
So, the one thing
more powerful
than the potion
is real love?
Bingo!
That took forever!
Why didn't you tell me?
You shut me away,
and you shut me up!
And Griselda
blames me for the
no-love-in-the-Dark-Forest!
Teaching moment.
There are
no shortcuts to love.
Just saying.
Stuff, take it away.
Okay, B.K. Here.
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait a minute!
This antidote
won't help Dawn.
She's never been
in love with anybody.
I shouldn't have
used the potion
on that poor, sweet...
Nothing would have been...
Real.
Well...
I know all about
getting your heart broken.
I almost married someone
who didn't love me.
Why?
He was so good-looking.
Oh.
Maybe I couldn't
bear to see
that he really was
a shallow, power-hungry,
cheating, chattering,
pig son of a...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Inside, I knew he
didn't want me to be...
You?
Yeah.
But you are
different.
I've been told.
That's what I like!
I mean, uh...
Well, you know.
So, now I keep
my guard up.
Me, too.
And most important,
I never...
Trust anybody!
Come on.
Let's go
stretch our wings.
Good idea! Good idea. Yes.
Here.
Thank you.
Hmm, maybe you should
rethink this entrance.
Try thinking of this
as an adventure!
Nice goblin.
Hey, how about we go back?
Why?
The moonlight
is perfect right now.
Come on,
"tough girl."
Uh...
♪ You're waking meadows
♪ In my mind
♪ Making waves
across my time
♪ Oh, no
Oh, no
♪ I got a strange magic
♪ Oh, what a strange magic
♪ Strange magic
♪ Oh, it's a strange magic
♪ Got a strange magic
♪ You're sailing
softly through the sun
♪ Softly through the sun
♪ Of a land I've always known
♪ You fly
♪ So high
♪ I get a strange magic
♪ Strange magic
♪ Oh, what a strange magic
♪ Oh, it's a strange magic
♪ Got a strange magic
♪ Oh, I
♪ Never gonna be
♪ Never gonna
be the same again
♪ Now I've seen
the way it's got to end
♪ Got to end
♪ Sweet dreams
♪ Got a strange magic
♪ Oh, what a strange magic
♪ Oh, it's a strange magic
♪ Got a strange magic
♪ It's magic
It's magic.
♪ It's magic ♪
It's...
Oh...
You...
You played me!
"Played you"?
I don't under...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Halt!
Disgusting creatures,
I come in peace.
I must get this
love potion
to your Bog King
by moondown.
I will need only three men.
My army will wait here.
Sandy.
It's Sunny.
You're in charge.
Me?
Look fierce.
Uh...
Fiercer!
Wait!
I won't be a fool again!
I didn't know!
I wouldn't follow me
if I were you, Princess.
You won't want to
see what I do to them.
I won't let that happen.
Ugh!
I am so stupid!
Execute plan on
my code word, "Go."
What kind of
odious throne is this?
Do something!
Uh...
Hold it, whoa, whoa,
hold it, hold it.
I'm here to give you this.
That is,
once you've given me...
Get the princess.
You mean
the princess-es...
Roland! What are you...
Restrain her!
No!
Oh! Hey!
He brought you
the potion!
Yes. And an army!
Well...
You got me to
leave my castle.
Clever girl.
But wasn't that your idea?
It was your idea!
And foolishly, I trusted you.
Wait a minute. Are you...
Are you actually
having a lovers' tiff
right now?
That is so disgusting!
It's interesting
but disgust...
Roland, you are such a...
Hero, to rescue you from...
What did you call him?
A scaly-backed cockroach.
Is that the guy?
Ugh.
Hey, Pare, I can't
stand it anymore.
I have to go find her.
You're in charge.
Uh...
What's going on?
Whoa!
Dawn! Are you down here?
- Hey, Sunny!
- You didn't listen!
What? Oh!
I said, "Stand in front!
Be the first she sees
when she..."
Please tell me
where Dawn is.
Okay, okay, I'll show you,
if you let us all out.
Which would be so sweet,
since this is all your fault!
Okay.
Yay!
My Boggy-woggy
Kingy-wingy.
Oh... I wish
I didn't see that.
This isn't...
I didn't mean for
any of this to happen.
Of course, uh,
I will be taking
both princesses.
That wasn't the deal.
No!
Deal's off.
Ugh. I wanted a wedding,
now I'm getting a funeral.
You leave my Boggy alone!
Hey! Oh!
"Bog."
What were you thinking?
A beast like you
falling for a beauty
like Marianne.
Who's the beast?
Stay out of it!
Hey! I can take
care of myself!
Two against one?
Not fair.
Roland! What are you...
Ah...
Let her go!
You're forcing me
to change my plan.
So,
sadly, now's the time
for me to
go!
Come on! We gotta hurry!
Oh, no.
Boy, oh boy, oh boy!
Keep it moving!
Especially you, Turtle!
What is happening?
No!
Marianne!
I have to find
your sister.
Okay.
And my mother.
My life is flashing
before my eyes.
Hey, I used to be hot.
You?
No time for chitchat.
Dawn!
Let go!
Sweetheart!
I'm gonna skewer your...
You will marry me!
Marianne!
We have to go.
Dawn! I'm coming!
Marianne! Get back!
Go!
Wait! Wait!
Bog!
My son.
Dawn!
You're all right.
You're really all right.
♪ Don't worry
About a thing
♪ 'Cause every little thing
♪ Gonna be all right
♪ Don't worry
About a thing ♪
Sunny?
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be... ♪
Sunny.
I love you.
Me?
You.
Mmm.
Are you
back?
Yeah.
But I don't know how.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Yahoo!
He's alive!
Bog!
My precious boy!
Ow!
Out of the way.
Move! Move!
King coming through.
Whoo-hoo!
No!
Marianne!
No! No, no, no!
Patience.
Ugh!
Here we go.
♪ Sugar pie, honey bunch
What?
Marianne?
♪ You know that I love you
That's what I wanna hear.
♪ I can't help myself
Of course not,
babycakes.
♪ I love... ♪
Whoa!
Ooh! It didn't work.
I wonder why.
Gosh, is that great!
I like that smell.
Aftershave?
No.
Is that cologne?
Well, boys, I've learned
a valuable lesson.
Never judge something
or someone
by how it or he or she
looks.
An elf!
Wait. Body lotion?
No.
Cold cream?
Ah! Got it! Deodorant.
It's perfume.
Nah. Are you a girl?
Isn't it obvious?
Huh?
It's kind of subtle.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Um...
Wings, shoulders, head,
all good.
You?
I'm good, too.
I just wanted to say,
I'll never see this place
the same way ever again.
Yeah.
Here.
It's hideous, but...
Yeah.
Then, um...
Bye!
Whoa!
I didn't mean
to sound so cute.
Cute actually works for you.
You know...
Yes?
Feel free to visit
whenever you like.
Oh. Okay.
Please don't sing!
You know what, Bog?
"Boggy."
It's never going
to work between us.
Well...
Shh! It's not you,
it's me.
No problem.
Yeah. No problem at all.
Marianne, a word.
I smell romance.
I hate that you always
hover and watch and worry!
I'm sorry?
But I love that you
came to this forest
to save me.
So, now,
I get to lecture you.
Huh?
♪ I know
something about love
♪ You've gotta want it bad
♪ If that guy's
got into your blood
♪ Go out and get him
♪ If you want him to be
♪ The very part of you
♪ That makes you
wanna breathe
♪ Here's the thing to do
♪ Tell him that
you're never gonna leave him
Tell him.
♪ Tell him that
you're always gonna love him
♪ Tell him
♪ Tell him!
My dear,
we need to have a talk.
Tell her how you feel.
♪ Tell her right now
♪ We know
something about love
♪ You've gotta show it and
♪ Make him see
the moon up above
♪ Reach out and get it
♪ If you want him to
♪ Make your heart sing out
♪ If you want her to
♪ Only think of you
♪ Tell him that
you're never gonna leave him
you're always gonna love him
♪ Tell him, tell him
Tell him
♪ Tell him right now
♪ Tell her right now
♪ Tell him that
you're never gonna leave him
♪ Tell her that
you're always gonna love her
♪ Tell her, tell her
♪ Tell her
Not that I'm nagging,
but...
♪ Tell her right now
♪ Tell him right now
Well, um, I...
♪ Right now ♪
Now!
Okay, okay.
Deep, deep
relaxing breaths.
♪ Wise men say
♪ Only fools rush in
♪ But I can't help
♪ Falling in...
♪ Falling in love with... ♪
Maybe I should
take it from here.
♪ Wild thing
♪ You make my heart sing
Oh!
♪ You make everything
♪ Groovy
♪ Oh, wild thing
♪ You make my heart sing
♪ You make everything
♪ Groovy
♪ Wild thing,
I think I love you!
♪ But I wanna know for sure
♪ Come on, hold me tight
♪ I love you
Uh-oh!
♪ You make me want to sing
♪ You make my heart
♪ You sing my song
You make my heart
♪ You make my
You make my
♪ You make my heart sing ♪
♪ Love
♪ Love is strange
♪ A lot of people
♪ Take it for a game
♪ Once you get it
♪ You're in an awful fix
♪ 'Cause after you've had it
♪ You never wanna quit
♪ Love is strange
♪ Love
♪ Is strange
♪ Oh, many people
♪ They don't understand
♪ They think loving
♪ Is money in the hand
♪ 'Cause sweet loving, hmm
♪ Is better than a kiss
♪ And when you leave
♪ Those kisses you will miss
♪ Love is strange
♪ Love
♪ Is strange
♪ Uh-uh ♪
It's far-out.
It's groovy.
Ah, it's so happening.
It's a weird trip, man.
Roland?
Roland!
Ignore them, sweetie.
Beauty is in
the eye of the beholder.
Oh, I think I got
one of your antennae.
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
Hmm.
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
♪ Don't you worry
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
♪ Oh, 'cause...
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
All right.
♪ Woke up this morning
♪ Smiled at the rising sun
♪ Three little birds
♪ Pitch by my doorstep
♪ Singin' sweet songs
♪ Of melodies pure and true
♪ Sayin'
♪ This is my message to you
♪ Hey, don't worry
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
♪ Oh, 'cause...
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
♪ Whoa!
♪ Don't you worry
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
♪ Oh, 'cause...
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
♪ Hey, it's gonna
be all right
♪ Whoo!
♪ Hey-ah!
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Hmm
♪ All right
♪ All right, right, right
♪ Hey, hey!
♪ Yeah
♪ Woke up this morning
♪ Smiled at the rising sun
♪ Three little birds
♪ Pitch by my doorstep
♪ Singin' sweet songs
♪ Of melodies
pure and true
♪ Sayin'
♪ This is my message to you
Sing it with me now!
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh
♪ Hey!
♪ Don't you worry
♪ Don't worry
♪ About a thing
♪ Oh, 'cause...
♪ 'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
♪ All right
♪ Hey! It's gonna
be all right
♪ It's gonna be all right
♪ Yeah
♪ Eh!
♪ Eh! ♪
Got it!
Tea Blend.
Huh?
Nailed it again.